Barbara B. Kennelly Papers
© 2004 University of Connecticut
Barbara B. Kennelly Papers.
undated, 1977-1998.
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center.
Kennelly, Barabara B.
79.3 linear feet.
Barbara Bailey Kennelly represented Connecticut in Congress for 17 years, leaving in 1999 as the highest ranking woman member in the history of the House of Representatives to that time. The collection includes correspondence to and from constituents and colleagues, notes, research materials, speeches, official congressional documents, congressional records, press clips, photographs, audio and video tapes, and special interest reports.
MSS19980369
Biography
Barbara Bailey Kennelly represented Connecticut in Congress for 17 years, leaving in 1999 as the highest ranking woman member in the history of the House of Representatives at that time. Her extensive career is the epitome of what a public servant should be, as she exhibited an unwavering dedication to helping those in need, most notably children, the elderly, and working families, not only in Connecticut but around the world. Throughout her political career, Ms. Kennelly fought for benevolent causes with strong conviction, and continues to do so today as the president of the National Committee to Preserve Social Security and Medicare in Washington, D.C..
Barbara Bailey was born into a politically active family 10 July 1936 in Hartford, Connecticut, where she was also raised. She received her B.A. in economics from Trinity College (Washington, D.C.) in 1958; a certificate in business administration from the Harvard Business School in 1959; and her M.A. in government from Trinity College (Hartford, Connecticut) in 1971. Over her career, she has also received several honorary doctorates from schools including Mount Holyoke College (South Hadley, Massachusetts); the University of Hartford (Hartford, Connecticut); Sacred Heart University (Bridgeport, Connecticut; and Saint Mary's College (South Bend, Indiana). She was married to the late James J. Kennelly, who worked as an attorney and served as a Connecticut State Representative and Speaker of the Connecticut House of Representatives, with whom she has three daughters and a son.
Heiress to the political legacy of her father, John Bailey, a longtime leader of the Connecticut Democratic Party and chairman of the Democratic National Committee, Barbara Kennelly entered politics in 1975 as a member of the Hartford Court of Common Council, a position she held until 1979 when she was elected Secretary of State for Connecticut. She served as Secretary until 1982, when she was elected to the 97th Congress by special election to fill the seat vacated upon the death of First District Representative William R. Cotter.
Kennelly served as Connecticut's First District Representative for the 97th through the 105th Congresses. She sat on many influential committees including Ways and Means, Budget, Administration, and Select Intelligence. Barbara Kennelly was only the third woman in history to serve on the 200-year-old House Ways and Means Committee and the first woman to chair one of the subcommittees of the House Intelligence Committee. In 1991, Kennelly was the first woman in United States history to be appointed Chief Deputy Majority Whip, where she served until her election as Caucus Vice Chair in 1994, the fourth ranking and the only woman in the elected leadership. She did not seek re-election for the 106th Congress, instead pursuing an unsuccessful campaign for the governorship of Connecticut.
Her legislative record reflects a deep commitment to working families, the elderly, children, and women. She championed legislation to enforce child support collection, give the working poor a tax break, and extend health care coverage to 10 million uninsured children. She was a strong advocate of Medicare and Social Security in addition to working to reform the Welfare system. Kennelly's career also included work for social justice with her repeated efforts to battle hate crimes.
Her legacy is one of a dedicated public servant, respected by Democrats and Republicans alike for her willingness to compromise while remaining true to those she represented. Barbara B. Kennelly currently resides in Hartford, Connecticut.
Scope and Content
The collection containes records compiled during Barbara Kennelly's legislative carreer. It includes correspondence to and from constituents and colleagues, notes, research materials, speeches, official congressional documents, congressional records, press clips, photographs, audio and video tapes, and special interest reports. There are no personal records of any kind, including correspondence. The only records pertaining to her gubernatorial campaign are press clips.
Arrangement
[Note: the following arrangement follows, as closely as possible, the creation of these records in Ms. Kennelly's Washington, D.C. office. To this end, several record types appear in multiple series since the records were created by different individuals with differing responsibilities over time, within the office. Folders containing materials created over several years are filed chronologically by the most recent year.]
Series I: Congressional Records ( 1982-1998 ) contains records pertaining to Barbara Kennelly's legislative work, organized chronologically by year and alphabetically by title therein. Includes the following subseries: A: Legislative Activity Guides, B: Legislative Profiles, C: House Voting Records, D: Record Statements, E: Voting Records - Interest Groups
Series II: Speeches ( 1979-1998 ) contains speeches delivered by Barbara Kennelly, organized chronologically. Note: additional speeches will be found filed under their relevant subject in Series V, with some duplication.
Series III: Press Releases ( 1982-1996 ) contains press releases issued by the office of Barbara Kennelly, organized chronologically. Note: additional press releases will be found filed under their relevant subject in Series V,with some duplication.
Series IV: Legislation ( 1981-1998 ) contains legislation generated by congress, organized chronologically by year and alphabetically therein by bill type and title. Note: additional pieces of legislation will be found filed under their relevant subject in Series V, with some duplication.
Series V: Subject Files ( 1977-1998 ) contains materials collected by Barbara Kennelly pertaining to her legislative work, and includes the following sub-series organized chronologically by year and alphabetically therein: A: Pre-congressional Career, B: 97th Congress, C: 98th Congress, D: 99th Congress, E: 100th Congress, F: 101st Congress, G: 102nd Congress, H: 103rd Congress, I: 104th Congress, J: 105th Congress, K: Date Unknown. Note: many subject files contain bills, speeches, press releases, and correspondence as they pertain to the subject.
Series VI: Correspondence ( 1982-1998 ) contains correspondence to and from Barbara Kennelly, organized chronologically by year and alphabetically by title therein. Note: many pieces of correspondence will be found filed under their relevant subject in Series V. The folders in this series have been left as ordered by the office of Barbara Kennelly.
Series VII: Writings ( 1982-1994 ) contains writings authored by Barbara Kennelly including editorials, newspaper articles, and newsletters, organized chronologically by year and alphabetically therein.
Sereis VIII: Bound Reports ( 1983-1985 ) contains bound reports issued to Kennelly.
Series IX: Press Clips ( 1982-1998 ) contains press clippings collected by Barbara Kennelly, organized chronologically by month and alphabetically by subject.
Series X: Media ( 1982-1998 ) contains various audio/visual media including videos, audio cassettes, photos, and negatives.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to Connecticut's Congressional delegation. See especially, Papers of William R. Cotter. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
DLC Speech Dodd 1998-0369.vr1
DLC: Making America Strong Dodd 1998-0369.vr2
Income Tax Credit PSA Dodd 1998-0369.vr3
Barbara Kennelly on CSPAN: Morning After Budget Passed 101st Congress Dodd 1998-0369.vr4
DLC Barbara Kennelly, March 10, 1989 Panel Dodd 1998-0369.vr5
Interview with Barbara Kennelly, 4/1/1991 Dodd 1998-0369.vr6
Separated Material
The following materials have been separated from the collection and cataloged:
1990 Census of population. Social and economic characteristics. Dodd Call No. C5691
The Constitution of the United States of America: analysis and interpretation. Dodd Call No. C5614
For better or for worse: marriage and the federal income tax. Dodd Call No. C5689
In the matter of Representative New Gingrich. Dodd Call No. C 5727, C5648, C5649
Investigation of the Office of the Postmaster. Dodd Call No. B5728
The record: gains and losses for women and families in the 104th Congress. Dodd Call No. C5688
Soul of Politics. Dodd Call No. C5615
The status of women in the States. Dodd Call No. C5616
Students' reports of school crime. Dodd Call No. C 5618
Where we stand Dodd Call No. C5617
The Hartford Club 'Women Who Dare' Series with former Congresswomen Barbara Kennelly and Nancy Johnson DVD 107
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Persons:
Kennelly, Barbara.
Family Names:
Kennelly.; Bailey.
Subjects:
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Publications.; Photographs.; Administrative Records.; Financial Records.; Minutes.; Press releases.; Videocassettes.; Audio cassettes.; Audio visual materials.; Fliers. [printed matter]; Photocopies.; Notes.; Books.; Interviews.; Speeches.; Resolutions.; Newsletters.; Newspapers.
Occupations:
Politician.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Acquisition Information
The collection was donated by Ms. Kennelly in 1998.
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series I: Congressional Records, 1982-1998
  - Voting Record and Roll Call Subject Guide - 97th Congress, 1982 (Box 1:, Folder 1)
  - Voting Record and Roll Call Subject Guide - 98th Congress, 1984 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
  - Voting Participation: House 1989-1990 (Box 1:, Folder 3)
  - DSG Vote Book - 101st Congress 2nd Session 1990 (1 of 2) (Box 1:, Folder 4)
  - DSG Vote Book - 101st Congress 2nd Session 1990 (2 of 2) (Box 1:, Folder 5)
  - Statistical Summary of Votes 102nd Congress, 1991-1992 (Box 1:, Folder 6)
  - Subseries A: Legislative Activity Guides, 1985-1998
    - 1985 (Box 1:, Folder 7-8)
    - 1986 (Box 1:, Folder 9-10)
    - 1988 (Box 1:, Folder 11-12)
    - 1989 (Box 1:, Folder 13-14)
    - 1990 (Box 2:, Folder 1-2)
    - 1991 (Box 2:, Folder 3)
    - 1992 (Box 2:, Folder 4-5)
    - 1993 (Box 2:, Folder 6)
    - 1994 (Box 2:, Folder 7-8)
    - 1995 (Box 2:, Folder 9)
    - 1996 (Box 2:, Folder 10)
    - 1997 (Box 2:, Folder 11-12)
    - 1998 (Box 2:, Folder 13-14)
  - Subseries B: Legislative Profiles, 1981-1997
    - 1981-1982 (Box 2:, Folder 15)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 2:, Folder 16-17)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 3:, Folder 1)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 3:, Folder 2)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 3:, Folder 3)
    - 1991 (Box 3:, Folder 4)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 3:, Folder 5-6)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 3:, Folder 7)
    - 1993 (Box 3:, Folder 8-11)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 3:, Folder 12-14)
    - 1993-1995 (Box 3:, Folder 15)
    - 1995 (Box 3:, Folder 16-17)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 3:, Folder 18-20)
    - 1997 (Box 3:, Folder 21)
  - Subseries C: House Voting Records, 1981-1998
    - 97th Congress, 1981-1982 (Box 4:, Folder 1)
    - 98th Congress, 1983-1984 (Box 4:, Folder 2)
    - 99th Congress, 1985-1986 (Box 4:, Folder 3)
    - 100th Congress, 1987-1988 (Box 4:, Folder 4)
    - 101st Congress, 1989-1990 (Box 4:, Folder 5)
    - 102nd Congress, 1991-1992 (Box 4:, Folder 6)
    - 103rd Congress, 1993-1994 (Box 4:, Folder 7)
    - 104th Congress, 1995-1996 (Box 4:, Folder 8)
    - 105th Congress, 1997-1998 (Box 4:, Folder 9)
    - House Votes 1982 (Box 4:, Folder 10)
    - House Votes 1983 (Box 4:, Folder 11)
    - House Votes 1984 (Box 4:, Folder 12)
    - House Votes 1985 (Box 4:, Folder 13)
    - House Votes 1986 (Box 4:, Folder 14)
    - House Votes 1987 (Box 4:, Folder 15)
    - House Votes 1988 (Box 4:, Folder 16)
    - House Votes 1989 (Box 4:, Folder 17)
    - House Votes 1990 (Box 4:, Folder 18)
    - House Votes 1991 (Box 4:, Folder 19)
    - House Votes 1992 (Box 4:, Folder 20)
    - House Votes 1993 (Box 4:, Folder 21)
    - House Votes 1994 (Box 4:, Folder 22)
    - House Votes 1995 (Box 4:, Folder 23)
    - House Votes 1996 (Box 4:, Folder 24)
    - House Votes 1997 (Box 4:, Folder 25)
    - House Votes 1998 (Box 4:, Folder 26)
  - Subseries D: Record Statements, 1981-1998
    - Congressional Record Remarks and Tributes 1982 (Box 4:, Folder 27)
    - Congressional Record Remarks and Tributes 1983 (Box 4:, Folder 28)
    - Congressional Record Remarks and Tributes 1984 (Box 4:, Folder 29)
    - Congressional Record Remarks and Tributes 1985 (Box 4:, Folder 30)
    - Congressional Record Remarks and Tributes 1986 (Box 4:, Folder 31)
    - Congressional Record Remarks and Tributes 1987 (Box 4:, Folder 32)
    - Congressional Record Remarks and Tributes 1988 (Box 4:, Folder 33)
    - Congressional Record Remarks and Tributes 1989 (Box 4:, Folder 34)
    - Congressional Record Remarks and Tributes 1990 (Box 4:, Folder 35)
    - Congressional Record Remarks and Tributes 1991 (Box 5:, Folder 1)
    - Congressional Record Remarks and Tributes 1992 (Box 5:, Folder 2)
    - Congressional Record Remarks and Tributes 1993 (Box 5:, Folder 3)
    - Congressional Record Remarks and Tributes 1994 (Box 5:, Folder 4)
    - Congressional Record Remarks and Tributes 1995 (Box 5:, Folder 5)
    - Congressional Record Remarks and Tributes 1996 (Box 5:, Folder 6)
    - Congressional Record Remarks and Tributes 1997 (Box 5:, Folder 7)
    - Congressional Record Remarks and Tributes 1998 (Box 5:, Folder 8)
    - Congressional Record - Statements 1989 (Box 5:, Folder 9)
    - Congressional Record - Statements 1990 (Box 5:, Folder 10)
    - Congressional Record - Statements 1991 (Box 5:, Folder 11)
    - Congressional Record - Statements 1992 (Box 5:, Folder 12)
    - Congressional Record - Statements 1994 (Box 5:, Folder 13)
    - Congressional Record - Statements 1995 (Box 5:, Folder 14)
    - Congressional Record - Statements 1996 (Box 5:, Folder 15)
    - Congressional Record - No. 153--Part II - Proceedings and Debates of the 97th Congress, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 16)
    - Congressional Record, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 17)
    - Congressional Record: 10th Anniversary ERA, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 18)
    - Congressional Record: Anniversary of Scharansky Imprisonment, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 19)
    - Congressional Record: Brian A. Bell Outstanding Airman of 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 20)
    - Congressional Record: Budget Cuts and Women, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 21)
    - Congressional Record: Child Welfare Forum, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 22)
    - Congressional Record: Commadore John Barry Day, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 23)
    - Congressional Record: ERA Reintroduction, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 24)
    - Congressional Record: Farewell to Sinai, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 25)
    - Congressional Record: Frank C. Schroll, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 26)
    - Congressional Record: Handicapped, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 27)
    - Congressional Record: HR5853, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 28)
    - Congressional Record: Ida Nudel, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 29)
    - Congressional Record: Ida Nudel, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 30)
    - Congressional Record: Ida Nudel's Special Order, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 31)
    - Congressional Record: Judiciary: Eliminate Gender Distinctions, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 32)
    - Congressional Record: Lelan F. Sillin Jr., 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 33)
    - Congressional Record: Low Income Fuel Program, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 34)
    - Congressional Record: NASA Authorization, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 35)
    - Congressional Record: Nuclear Weapons, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 36)
    - Congressional Record: Simon Amendment, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 37)
    - Congressional Record: Social Security Amendment (Box 5:, Folder 38)
    - Congressional Record: Swearing In, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 39)
    - Congressional Record: Tribute to Toby Moffett, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 40)
    - Congressional Record: University of Hartford 25th, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 41)
    - Congressional Record: Vending Machines, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 42)
    - Congressional Record: Women's History Week, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 43)
    - Congressional Record: Yom Hashoa Celebration, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 44)
    - 97th Congress: Calendars of United States House of Representatives, 1981 (Box 5:, Folder 45)
  - Subseries E: Voting Records -Interest Groups, 1981-1998
    - 97th Congress - 1981-1982 (Box 5:, Folder 46)
    - 98th Congress - 1983-1984 (Box 5:, Folder 47)
    - 99th Congress - 1985-1986 (Box 5:, Folder 48)
    - 100th Congress - 1987-1988 (Box 5:, Folder 49)
    - 101st Congress - 1989-1990 (Box 5:, Folder 50-51)
    - 102nd Congress - 1991-1992 (Box 5:, Folder 52)
    - 103rd Congress - 1993-1994 (Box 5:, Folder 53)
    - 104th Congress - 1995-1996 (Box 5:, Folder 54)
    - 105th Congress - 1997-1998 (Box 5:, Folder 55)
- Series II: Speeches, 1979-1998
  - 1979 (Box 6:, Folder 1)
  - 1980 January - May (Box 6:, Folder 2)
  - 1980 June - December (Box 6:, Folder 3)
  - 1980 (Box 6:, Folder 4)
  - 1981 January - May (Box 6:, Folder 5)
  - 1981 June - December (Box 6:, Folder 6)
  - 1981 (Box 6:, Folder 7)
  - 1982 January - April (Box 6:, Folder 8)
  - 1982 May (Box 6:, Folder 9)
  - 1982 June (Box 6:, Folder 10)
  - 1982 July - December (Box 6:, Folder 11)
  - 1982 (Box 6:, Folder 12)
  - 1983 January - August (Box 6:, Folder 13)
  - 1983 September - December (Box 6:, Folder 14)
  - 1983 (Box 6:, Folder 15)
  - 1984 January - April (Box 6:, Folder 16)
  - 1984 May (Box 6:, Folder 17)
  - 1984 June - August (Box 6:, Folder 18)
  - 1984 September - December (Box 6:, Folder 19)
  - 1984 (Box 6:, Folder 20)
  - 1985 January - June (Box 7:, Folder 1)
  - 1985 July - December (Box 7:, Folder 2)
  - 1985 (Box 7:, Folder 3)
  - 1986 January - February (Box 7:, Folder 4)
  - 1986 March - December (Box 7:, Folder 5)
  - 1986 (Box 7:, Folder 6)
  - 1987 January - June (Box 7:, Folder 7)
  - 1987 July - December (Box 7:, Folder 8)
  - 1987 (Box 7:, Folder 9)
  - 1988 January - May (Box 7:, Folder 10)
  - 1988 June - August (Box 7:, Folder 11)
  - 1988 September - December (Box 7:, Folder 12)
  - 1988 (Box 7:, Folder 13)
  - 1989 January - March (Box 7:, Folder 14)
  - 1989 April (Box 7:, Folder 15)
  - 1989 May - August (Box 7:, Folder 16)
  - 1989 September - December (Box 7:, Folder 17)
  - 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 18)
  - 1990 January - March (Box 8:, Folder 1)
  - 1990 April - June (Box 8:, Folder 2)
  - 1990 July - December (Box 8:, Folder 3)
  - 1990 (Box 8:, Folder 4)
  - 1991 January - February (Box 8:, Folder 5)
  - 1991 March - April (Box 8:, Folder 6)
  - 1991 May - December (Box 8:, Folder 7)
  - 1991 (Box 8:, Folder 8)
  - 1992 January (Box 8:, Folder 9)
  - 1992 February (Box 8:, Folder 10)
  - 1992 March - April (Box 8:, Folder 11)
  - 1992 May - June (Box 8:, Folder 12)
  - 1992 July - December (Box 8:, Folder 13)
  - 1992 (Box 8:, Folder 14)
  - 1993 January - September (Box 8:, Folder 15)
  - 1993 October - December (Box 8:, Folder 16)
  - 1993 (Box 8:, Folder 17)
  - 1994 January - April (Box 9:, Folder 1)
  - 1994 May - December (Box 9:, Folder 2)
  - 1994 (Box 9:, Folder 3)
  - 1995 January - May (Box 9:, Folder 4)
  - 1995 June - December (Box 9:, Folder 5)
  - 1995 (Box 9:, Folder 6)
  - 1996 (Box 9:, Folder 7)
  - 1998 (Box 9:, Folder 8)
  - undated (Box 9:, Folder 9-10)
- Series III: Press Releases, 1982-1996
  - 1982 (Box 10:, Folder 1)
  - 1983 (Box 10:, Folder 2)
  - 1984 (Box 10:, Folder 3)
  - 1985 (Box 10:, Folder 4)
  - 1986 (Box 10:, Folder 5)
  - 1987 (Box 10:, Folder 6)
  - 1988 (Box 10:, Folder 7)
  - 1989 (Box 10:, Folder 8)
  - 1990 (Box 10:, Folder 9)
  - 1991 January - August (Box 10:, Folder 10)
  - 1991 September - December (Box 10:, Folder 11)
  - 1992 (Box 10:, Folder 12)
  - 1993 (Box 10:, Folder 13)
  - 1994 January - August (Box 10:, Folder 14)
  - 1994 September - December (Box 10:, Folder 15)
  - 1995 January - July (Box 10:, Folder 16)
  - 1995 August - December (Box 10:, Folder 17)
  - 1996 (Box 10:, Folder 18)
- Series IV: Legislation, 1981-1998
    - H Con Res 100 - Calendar: Pentasoctal Families, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 1)
    - H Con Res 151 - Calendar: Elimination of Nuclear Arms, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 2)
    - H Res 252 - Calendar: Clean Air Resolution, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 3)
    - H Res 252 - Energy and Commerce: Clean Air Resolution, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 4)
    - H Res 268 - Calendar: Sex Discrimination in Education, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 5)
    - H Res 302 - Calendar: Added Qualifications for Members, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 6)
    - H Res 309 - Calendar: Air Traffic Controlers, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 7)
    - H Res 309 - Post Office: Patco Resolution, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 8)
    - H Res 364 - Calendar: Day of National Celebration - George Washington, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 9)
    - H Res 371 - Calendar: Annual National POW/MIA Day, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 10)
    - HJ Res 151 - Square Dance as National Folk Dance, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 11)
    - HJ Res 316 - Calendar: National Nurse Midwifery Week, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 12)
    - HJ Res 317 - Calendar: Peace in the Mideast, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 13)
    - HJ Res 332 - Calendar: National Home Healthcare Week, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 14)
    - HJ Res 354 - Calendar: 1982 National Year of Disabled, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 15)
    - HJ Res 359 - Calendar: National Disabled Veterans Week, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 16)
    - HJ Res 363 - Calendar: Municipal Clerks Week, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 17)
    - HJ Res 375 - Calendar: National Orchestra Week, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 18)
    - HR 808 - Amend the Immigration and Nationality Act, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 19)
    - HR 1799 - Banking: Export Trade Act, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 20)
    - HR 1918 - Veteran's Affairs: WWI Veterans Service Pension Act, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 21)
    - HR 2500 - Education and Labor: Select Commision on Voluntary Service, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 22)
    - HR 2828 - Banking: State Government Financing Reform Act, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 23)
    - HR 3039 - Armed Services: Military Spouse Retirement Equity, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 24)
    - HR 3117 - Ways and Means - Economic Equity Act, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 25)
    - HR 3973 - Post Office: Amend Title 39, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 26)
    - HR 4086 - Judiciary: Citizenship for Wladyslaw Stanizewski, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 27)
    - HR 4147 - Public Works: Travel Agent Bill, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 28)
    - HR 4547 - Ways and Means - New London Day, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 29)
    - HR 4588 - Foreign Affairs: Hunger Prevention and Food Security, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 30)
    - HR 4710 - Judiciary: Alimony, Child Support, Etc., 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 31)
    - HR 4767 - Judiciary: FBI in Police Killings, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 32)
    - HR 4786 - Judiciary: Bankruptcy Improvements of 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 33)
    - HR 4829 - Energy and Commerce: Acid Rain, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 34)
    - HR 4861 - Interior: Public Lands Conservation Act, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 35)
    - HR 4873 - Banking: Medal to Widow of Roy Wilkens, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 36)
    - HR 5006 - Energy and Commerce: National Institute on Arthritis, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 37)
    - HR 5088 - Foreign Affairs: U.S. Academy of Peace, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 38)
    - HR 5127 - Judiciary: National Federation of Music Clubs, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 39)
    - HR 5180 - Ways and Means - Hospice Care, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 40)